In this segment, we are going to discuss the tools that you use working with glass.
So first off obviously, is to start your torch you are going to need the igniter.
Now this is just your average igniter for your grill or whatever starts a little bit the flame.
From beyond that we carry on to some tweezers which comes in many different sizes some big guys, some smaller ones here, we got ones with different edges and tips.
Here we have a pick to is for picking and dragging color through your glass art.
Here we have a graphite rimer.
A graphite is very important with glass because the glass does not stick to the graphite when the glass is blown.
Beyond that we are going to use glass shears which we can cut glass in high temperature.
Here we have a marble mobber which is a hand held mobber hand you can round off ends off whatever you are working on.
If you do it good enough, you can do a mobber.
Here is just a big graphite paddle this is used for all sorts of dimensions and to shape things with your glass.
The last one we are going to discuss here are the bead masher which would give you parallel edges whenever you are working which can finish out any kind of project.
Any or all combination with these tools, you can also make sweet glass art.